wa-com.com 2018-11-24

# Privacy policy - wa-com.com

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 22-06-2013 

**Whois informations**

Whois information is public, in order to protect personals informations you should enable the privacy protect option when registering your website. We update informations as fast as we can but delay may happen, to request an automatic update of your whois record use the button situated in the concerned page or contact us for an update, we will try to respond quickly. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

website : wa-com.com

contact@accuracy-technology.com

This policy is powered by Trust Guard [PCI compliance](http://www.trust-guard.com/PCI-Compliance-s/65.htm).
